benefito.com 2011-12-09

# Free online classifieds. Benefito free classified ads.

| 

###  Benefito Privacy Policy

Benefito Inc. knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust. We do NOT sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting Benefito.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

#### What Personal Information About Customers Does Benefito.com Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve services at Benefito.com. We receive and store securely any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.

#### Does Benefito.com Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with subsidiaries of Benefito Inc., controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. 

#### Children

Benefito.com does not list services provided for children. If you are under 18, you may use Benefito.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

#### Unauthorized Users

It is possible that other Registered Users or users (including unauthorized users, or "hackers") may post or transmit offensive or obscene materials on the Service and that you may be involuntarily exposed to such offensive and obscene materials. It also is possible for others to obtain personal information about you due to your use of the Service, and that the recipient may use such information to harass or injure you. Benefito Inc. is not responsible for the use of any personal information that you disclose on the Service. Please carefully select the type of information that you post on the Service or release to others.

#### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 

If you choose to visit Benefito.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our User Agreement, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Pennsylvania. If you have any concern about privacy at Benefito.com, please send us a thorough description through feedback, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the User Agreement will change constantly also. You should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

We use Google, a third party vendor, to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, click [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

#### More Information

If you have additional questions, please contact us at any time at support@benefito.com.  
  
---|---
